Benjamin H. Wolf Papers 5305
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Simmons Co. vs. Local 420, UIU, 3/17/69, #68-419, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Decision - Violation of Arbitrator's Award
- Kraft Foods Co. vs. Local 56, Amalgamated Food and Allied Workers (AFAW), 6/3/69. #68-424, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Decision, Hearing Transcripts - Assignment to work outside classification
- Ramapo Board of Education vs. Ramapo-Indian Hills Association, 12/20/68. #68-425, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Recommendations of Fact- Finder - Contract Negotiation
- United States Pipe & Foundry Co. vs. Local 2026, USWA, 3/17/69. #68-426, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Decision - Vacancies
- Newark Newspaper Publishers on behalf of the Evening News vs. Local 3, Newark Typographical Union, 3/3/69. #68-427, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Jericho Motors Inc. vs. Local 355, Amalgamated Union, 3/12/69. #68-428, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Decision - Inefficiency
- Starlight Co. Inc. vs. Local 54, IBPSPMW, 4/30/69. #68-430, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Decision - Retirement
- Airco Welding Products, Inc. vs. Local 315, IAM, 4/7/69. #69-431, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Subcontracting
- New Jersey Highway Authority and Local 196, American Federation of Technical Employees (AFTE) and Garden State Parkway Employees Assn. and Garden State Parkway Maintenance Employees Assn., 1/25/69. #69-432, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendations, Hearing Transcripts, personnel Policies, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits - Bargaining Units, Representation Proceedings
- Sealtest Foods vs. Local 607, IBT, 1/31/69. #69-434, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  Decision - Dishonesty
- Consolidated Freightways vs. Local 560, IBT, 3/17/69. #69-436, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  Decision - Improper Possession of Company Policy
- Harbor Distributing Co. vs. Local 46, IBT, 3/5/69. #69-437, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  Decision - Work Stoppage
- Village of Scarsdale vs. Scarsdale Uniform Firemen's Assn., 7/5/69. #69-440, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendations - Contract Negotiations
- Suburban Transfer Service Inc. vs. Local 804, IBT, 4/2/69. #69-441, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Atkins Chevrolet, Inc. vs. Local 4, IBT, 9/2/69. #69-443, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  Decision - Arbitrability, Contract Modification
- Stella D'Oro Biscuit Co., Inc. vs. Local 50, ABCWU, 5/27/69. #69-444, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  Decision - Contract Interpretation, Wages
- Central School District #1, Somers, NY vs. Somers Faculty Assn., 5/27/69. #69-446, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendations - Contract Negotiations (Salary Schedules, Fringe Benefits)
- Evans Rule Co. vs. District 19, USAW, 4/69. #69-447, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Allen Crane & Hoist Co. vs. Shopmen's Local 455. 4/10/69. #69-450, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  Decision, Hearing Transcript - Discrimination
- Bamberger's New Jersey vs. Local 177, IBT, 5/69. #69-449, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  Decision - Vacations & Vacation Pay
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT, 6/16/69. #69-450, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Village of Scarsdale vs. Scarsdale Police Benevolent Assn., 6/11/69. #69-452, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendations - Contract negotiations
- Eastchester Schools, Bd. Of Education vs. Eastchester Teachers Assn., 5/19/69. #69-453 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendations - Contract Negotiation
- City of New York vs. Local 983, AFSCME, 7/69. #69-454, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendations, Hearing Transcripts - Contract Negotiation
- Village of North Tarrytown vs. North Tarrytown Police Bargaining Committee, 5/1/69. #69-455, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  Finding of Facts & Recommendations - Contract Negotiations
- The Herald News vs. Local 660, PPU, 9/15/69. #69-456, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, General Correspondence - Repayment of Monies to Employer
- Fink Baking Corporation vs. Local 3, BCW, 1/10/62, 1962 (Box 10.1, Folder 1)
- Queens Farms Dairy Co., Inc. vs. Local 584, IBT, 6/30/69. #69-457, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Decision, General Correspondence - Red Circle Rates
- Board of Education, Ramapo-Indian Hills Regional High School District vs. Ramapo-Indian Hills Education Assn., Inc., 6/6/69. #69-458, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendation, Fact-Finders Notes, Exhibits, General Correspondence, Contract Negotiation
- Board of Education, Ossining, NY, vs. Ossining Teachers Assn., 4/18/69. #69-459, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Fact Finder's Notes, Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract negotiations
- Nu Boro Park Cleaners & Dyers Inc. vs. Local 239, ACWA, 5/6/69. #69-460, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Incompetence
- National Can Corporation vs. Local 15, IAM, 9/11/69. #69-461, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Brief, Employer Brief, Past LA Awards, Employer Exhibits, General Correspondence - Sick Pay
- Institutional Inspectors vs. Dist. Council 37, AFSCME, 9/25/69. #69-462, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Fact-Finder's Notes, Exhibits, Newspaper Clippings, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- Wilson Freight Co. vs. Local 560, IBT, 6/13/69. #69-463, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Miscellaneous notes, correspondence - insubordination
- Ciba Pharmaceutical Co. vs. Local 9, ICWU, 6/9/69. #69-464, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence
- Tarrytown Board of Education vs. Tarrytown Teacher's Association, 5/69. #69-465, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Fact-Finder's Notes, exhibits, correspondence
- Allied Maintenance Co. vs. Local 30, IUOE, 5/12/69. #69-466, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Decision, Arbitrator's notes, Employer exhibits, employee exhibits, correspondence- improper work practices
- John Stuart, Inc. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 5/13/69. #69-467, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Correspondence - Termination
- Vulcan Fuel Corporation vs. Local 553, IBT, 1/11/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 1)
  Decision - Discharge, Absences, Carelessness
- Mercury Furniture Corp. vs. District 65, RWDSU, 1/17/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 2)
- Brevel Products Corporation vs. Local 431, IUE, 1/18/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 3)
- Craftex Comfort Products, Inc. vs. Local 422, IPSSEU, 1/22/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 4)
- Crystal Maid Manufacturing Corporation vs. Textile Workers of America, 2/1/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 5)
- Potato Service Co. of NY vs. Local 719, International Production Service and Sales Employees Union, 2/1/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 6)
- Inner Circle vs. Local 1, Dining Room Employees Union, 2/5/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 7)
  Decision - Leaves of Absence, Medical Release
- Joseph Albertelli d/b/a M & A Bakery vs. Local 150, Bakery Salesmen, 2/11/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 8)
- Hill's Supermarkets, Inc. vs. Local 1500, RCIA, 2/13/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 9)
  Decision - Discharge, Moonlighting
- Everlast Process Printing Co. vs. Local 51, NY Printing Pressmen's Union, 2/13/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 10)
- Glassman Box Corp. vs. Local 76B, UFW, 3/8/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 11)
- Honerkamp Plywood Co. vs. Local 138, IBT, 3/20/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 12)
- Twix Manufacturing Co. vs. Local 463, IUE, 3/20/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 13)
- 848 Empire Inc. vs. Local 1, Waitress Union, 3/21/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 14)
- Cake Fair vs. Local 150, RCIA, 3/27/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 15)
- Treco Mattress Co., Inc. vs. Local 140, UFW, 3/28/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 16)
- Eagle Brands Products Inc. vs. Local 174, Butchers Union, 4/1/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 17)
  Decision - Discharge, Lay-off, Seniority
- Roy Weaving Co., Inc. vs. N.Y. Jt. Board, TWU, 4/17/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 18)
- Taffet Electronics Inc. vs. Local 295, IBT, 4/17/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 19)
  Decision - Discharge, Fights & Altercations
- Hill Manufacturing Corp. vs. Local 275, maintenance Employees Union of Greater NY, 4/22/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 20)
- Acorn Restaurant Inc. vs. Local 164, Hotel and Restaurant Employees & Bartenders Union, 4/29/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 21)
- Shamrock Wrecking Co. vs. Local 95, Housewreckers Union, 5/2/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 22)
  Decision - Hiring, Union Security
- 2449-53 7th Avenue and 152 W. 143rd St. vs. Local 90 Organized Workers Union of Building Service Employees Union, 4/30/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 23)
- Able Wrecking Corporation vs. Local 95, Housewreckers Union, 5/2/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 24)
- Scent Sation, Inc. vs. Local 44, Service & Production Employees Union, 5/2/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 25)
- Scala Contracting Co. vs. Local 95, Housewrecker's Union, 5/2/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 26)
  Decision - Hiring, Lay-off
- Scranton Lehigh Coal Co. vs. Local 553, IBT, 5/6/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 27)
- Ford Instrument Co. vs. Local 471, IUE, 5/28/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 28)
  Decision - Classification of Jobs, Promotion
- Alumaweld Products, Inc. vs. United Brotherhood of Aluminum and Metal Workers, 6/5/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 29)
  Decision - Inability to Work, Rates of Pay
- Kurman Instrument Company vs. Local 431, IUE, 6/6/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 30)
- Lieco, Inc. vs. District 15, IAM, 6/7/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 31)
- Chain Bike Corporation vs. Local 1614, IBEW, 6/7/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 32)
- Valentine Realty Corporation vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 6/14/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 33)
  Decision - Discharge, Negligence & Carelessness
- 1963 Daly Avenue Realty Corp. vs. Local 32E, BSEIU, 6/14/63 (Box 11.1, Folder 34)
- Lipsett Demolition vs. Local 95, Housewrecker's Union, 6/27/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 35)
- Adams Laboratories, Inc. vs. Local 431, IUE, 7/10/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 36)
  Decision - Rates of Pay, Merit Increases
- Concord Oil Corporation vs. Local 1922, IBEW, 7/15/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 37)
- Mueller Steam Specialty Co., Inc. vs. Local 1146, RCIA, 7/16/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 38)
  Decision - Lunch Periods, Schedules of Work
- National Gypsum Co. vs. District 50, UMW, 7/30/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 39)
- Palizzio, Inc. vs. Jt. Council 13, United Shoe Workers of America, 8/2/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 40)
- Continental Baking Co., Inc. vs. Local 50, ABCWU, 8/27/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 41)
- Whitehouse Products, Inc. vs. Jt. Board of Greater NY of the International Leather Goods, Plastics, and Novelty Workers Union, 8/30/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 42)
- Andrew Geller, Inc. vs. Jt. Council, 13, United Shoe Workers of America, 8/30/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 43)
  Decision - Rates of pay; Incentive pay
- East River Consolidators, Inc. vs. Local 807, IBT, 9/6/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 44)
- Weisner & Son's vs. Local 1, Independent Union of Building Service Employees, 9/6/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 45)
- Dallek, Inc. vs. Local 210, IBT, 9/10/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 46)
  Decision - Vacation Pay, Severance Pay
- Daily Toiletries Inc. vs. Local 875, IBT, 9/10/63, 1963 (Box 11.1, Folder 47)
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT, 3/19/70. #69-468 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Decision, Hearing Transcripts, Employer Briefs, Employee Briefs, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibit, Correspondence - Assignment of Work Outisde Classification
- The Exolon Co. vs. USWA, 8/20/69. #69-469, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Statement of Issue, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Incompetence
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. Local 212, IBEW, 8/18/69, #69-470, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Improper Personal Conduct
- New Rochelle Bd. Of Education vs. New Rochelle Teachers Federation, 5/69; 8/29/69. #69-471, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Decisions, Contract, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibits, School Directory, General Correspondence - Bargaining in Good Faith, Retroactive Pay
- Educational Broadcasting Corp. of New York, WNDT, Channel 13 vs. Local 1212, IBEW, 7/69., 1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Rates of Pay
- Direct Mail Master vs. District 65, RWDSU, 6/24/69. #69-473, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties During Hearing
- Weston Instruments, Inc. vs. Weston Employees Independent, 7/7/69. #69-474, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Decision, arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Union Contract, Correspondence - Arbitrability
- F.W. Woolworth Co. vs. Local 804, IBT, 9/19/59. #69-475, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Decision, Employer Brief, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Correspondence - Retirement
- New York Air Brake Co. vs. Local 761, IAM, 12/15/69. #69-476, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Contract, Correspondence - Classification of Jobs
- Williams Press, Inc. vs. Local 23, APPAOWU, 6/25/69. #69-477, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's notes, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Elimination of Jobs
- Toms River Chemical Corp. vs. Toms River Chemical Employees Union, 9/68, #69-478, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- PPG Industries Inc. vs. Local 1, Allied Chemical and Alkali Workers (ACAW), 9/69 #69-479, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Correspondence - No Decision - Hearing Delayed
- Dean Products vs. Local 810, IBT, 8/26/69. #69-480, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Union Representatives, Past Practice
- Newark Broadcasting Corp. vs. Local 1212, IBEW, 11/69. #69-481, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Contract, Correspondence - Waiver of Seniority
- Orange & Rockland Utilities, Inc. vs. Local 1567, IBEW, 11/69. #69-482, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  Decision, Hearing Transcripts, Employer Briefs, Employee Briefs, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Incompetence & Absences
- Kops-Monahan Communications vs. NABET, 9/69. #69-483, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Correspondence - Grievance Withdrawn by Grievant
- Joy Manufacturing Co. vs. Lodge 72, IAM, 12/69. #69-484, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- CPC International vs. Best Foods Employees Assn., 10/69. #69-485, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Mack Trucks Inc. vs. Local 259, UAW, 9/69. #69-486, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Newark Board of Education vs. the Newark Teachers' Assn. 8/14/69. #69-487, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibits, Employee Newspaper, Joint Exhibits, Contract, Correspondence - Contract Modification
- KPT Manufacturing Co. vs. Local 47, IAM, 10/69. #69-488, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- National Gypsum Co. vs. Local 8-247, OCAWIU, 11/25/69. #69-489, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Decision, arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Vacancies
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT, 5/6/70. #69-490, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Decision, Hearing Transcript, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Briefs, Employee Briefs, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Elimination of Jobs
- Daltrui Industries vs. Federal Labor Union 22026, 10/3/69. #69-492, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Assignment of New Jobs
- The City of New Rochelle vs. District Council 37, AFSCME, 10/16/69. #69-493, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendation, Fact-Finder's Notes, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, General Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- Hatco Chemical Div., W.R. Grace & Co. vs. Local 102, IBT, 10/69. #69-494, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Williams Press vs. Local 23, APPAOWU, 9/23/69. #69-495, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, General Correspondence - Crew Size
- Northwest Airlines, Inc. vs. Air Line Pilots Assn., 10/69. #69-496, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Target Rock Corp. vs. Local 431, 11/69. #69-497, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Silvercrest Farms, Inc. vs. Local 584, IBT. #69-498 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Correspondence - No Follow Up Decision
- Okanite Co. vs. Local 1992, OBEW, 10/69. #69-499, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Civil Action Claim, Answer & Counterclaim, Correspondence - Insurance
- Board of Education, City School District, Mount Vernon, NY vs. Mt. Vernon Fed. Of Teachers, 12/18/69. #69-500, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibits, Contract, Correspondence - Transfers
- City of New York, Office of Labor Relations, vs. Local 300, Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1/13/70. #69-501, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendations, Hearing Transcripts, Fact-Finder's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract (Wage Settlement)
- Wilbar Photoengraving Co., Inc. vs. Local 1-P, New York Lithographers & Photoengravers, 1/9/70. #69-502 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Subcontracting, Severance Pay
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT, 12/22/69. #69-503, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  Decision, Hearing Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Interpretation - Leave of Absence (maternity leave)
- Teleflex Inc. vs. Local 1039, UAW, 12/17/69. #69-504, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Overtime
- The City of Yonkers vs. Yonkers Firemen's Mutual Aid Association, 12/2/69. #69-505, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Findings of Fact & Recommendations, Fact-Finder's Notes, Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- Madison Township Board of Education vs. Madison Township Educational Assn., 2/9/70. #69-506, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Decision, Hearing Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Contract, Employees Proposed Agreement, Correspondence - Arbitrability, Probationary Period
- Ocean View Retreat Nursing Home vs. Local 1115, NHHSCHU, 1/70. #69-508, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  Correspondence - Request for Arbitration
- Atlantic Highlands Nursing Home vs. Local 1115, NHHSCHU, 1/70. #69-509, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Contract, Correspondence - Mutually Settled by Parties
- R.H. Macy & Co., Inc. vs. Local 1-S, RWDSU, 12/5/69. #69-509, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Decision, arbitrator's Notes, Contract, Correspondence - Timeliness
- GAF Corp. vs. Local 306, ICW, 9/1/70. #69-510, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- West Penn Power Co. vs. Local 102, Utility Workers Union (UWU), 12/69. #69-511, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  Correspondence
- Spaulding Fibre Co., Inc. vs. Lodge 2106, IAM, 3/10/70. #69-512, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Rates of pay
- Borough of Ringwood vs. Local 1960, AFSCME, 12/15/69. #69-513, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Findings of Recommendation, Mediator's Notes, Miscellaneous Information, Newspaper Clippings, Correspondence - Inclusion in Bargaining Unit
- Cast Optics Corp. vs. Textile Wkrs. Of America, 7/1/70. #69-514, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  Decision, hearing Transcripts (not complete), Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Briefs, Employee Briefs, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Court Orders, Correspondence - Arbitrability, Timeliness, Strike, Contract Modification, Union Security, Insurance, Vacation
- Trust Co. of New Jersey vs. Local 142, OPEIU, 12/31/69. #69-515, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreed Submission, Employer Exhibits, Contract, Correspondence - Absences & Tardiness
- Board of Education of Ramapo-Indian Hills Regional High School District vs. Ramapo-Indian Hills Education Assn., 2/5/70, #69-516, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employee Exhibits, Contract Correspondence - Compensatory Time-off
- Williams Press, Inc. vs. Local 23, APPAOWU, 12/8/69, 12/22/69, 3/20/70, 4/23/70. #69-517, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Decisions, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, General Exhibits, Constitution, Contracts, Correspondence - Seniority (priority list), Shift Preference, Rates of Pay, Absences (Part-time Employee)
- Signal Delivery Service Co. vs. Local 469, IBT, n.d. #69-518 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Lowe Paper Co. vs. Local 11, IBT, 1/28/70, #69-519, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Rates of Pay, Classification of Jobs, Recall
- Briggs Leasing Corp. vs. Local 259, UAW, #69-520 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT, 6/29/70. #70-521, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Decision, hearing Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Retention Rights, Dual Employment
- Board of Education, City of Camden vs. Camden Education Association, 1/22/70. #70-522, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Finding of Fact & Recommendation, Fact-Finder's Notes, Exhibits, Contract, Proposals for New Contract, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations
- South Orangetown Central School Dist. 1 vs. Education Assn. of South Orangetown, 1/28/70. #70-523, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibits, Correspondence - Contract Interpretation, Salary Schedules
- Board of Education of City of New York vs. UFT, 12/31/70. #70-524, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  Decision, Hearing Transcript, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Past Arbitration Awards, Correspondence - Grievance Procedure, Compensatory Time
- City of new York vs. American Newspaper Guild, 1/70. #70-525, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Correspondence - Mediation Ceased, Impasse Exists
- The Federal Bearings Co., Inc. vs. Local 297, UAW, 2/5/70. #70-526, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Statement of Settlement, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Schedule of Work
- Webster Lens Co. vs. Local 408, UOWU, IUE, 3/70. #70-527, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Decision, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Exhibit, Joint Exhibit, Correspondence - Bidding, Promotion
- Silvercrest Farms vs. Local 584, IBT, n.d. #70-528 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Board of Education of the City of New York vs. UFT re Leslie Lubin, 6/4/70. #70-529, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Decision, hearing Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Employer Brief, Employee Brief, Employer Exhibit, Employee Exhibits, Joint Exhibits, Correspondence - Arbitrability, Employee's File
- Anheuser-Busch, Inc. vs. Local 102, IBT, 3/70. #70-530, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- New York Keansburg-Long Branch Bus Co. vs. Local 701, IBT, n.d. #70-531 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Lowe Paper Co. vs. Local 11, IBT, 3/70. #70-532, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- USDESEA vs. Overseas Education Assn., 2/70. #70-533, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  Mediator's Report, Mediator's Notes, Contract, Exhibits, Correspondence - Grievance Procedure
- Fair Lawn Board of Education vs. Fair Lawn Education Assn., 3/16/70. #70-534, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  Arbitrator's Notes, Correspondence - Mutually Solved by Parties During Arbitration Hearings
- The City of New York vs. Local 3, ANG, re: Photographer, 10/7/70.#70-535, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  Findings of Facts & Recommendations, Hearing Transcripts, Mediator's Notes, Employer Exhibits, Employee Exhibits, Dissent by ANG, Correspondence - Contract Negotiations (Salary Schedules), Classification of Jobs
- Albany Steel Co. vs. Local 469, IBT, 8/70. #70-536, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)